You know... You really messed up this time.
Dad's still pissed. You're honestly lucky
this is the extent of your punishment.
I'm sorry, Onee-chan...
#3 "They Show Up When You Least Expect It"
Tanisaki Bread
Yes, thank you very much.
Hey, those two girls were first.
I was watching.
Yoshino!
Y-Yes, Aki-sama?
I need you to add five rice balls
to that order of breads.
All right.
Honestly...
What's everyone's problem?!
First comes muscles...
Second comes muscles...
There's no third or fourth...
Fifth comes muscles...
M-Master?
Deodorizing
Mist
Unscented
I'm surprised you knew I was here.
The student store is right below here.
I thought I heard some creepy yelling.
Don't say it's creepy.
Running away to your muscles
isn't going to change Aki-sama.
Salmon
But seriously, that's so much food.
She's been eating more again as of late.
She hasn't changed?
Basically, no. But she's
gotten a little sloppier.
Oh... I see.
Damn it! How is she able to
twist the truth so much?
You don't have any idea,
either, right? It's insane.
Aki-sama was going through a lot back then...
So she might be confused.
So she conveniently manipulated
her memories for her own sake.
Well, anyway, Aki-sama's starving.
Pig's Foot, I'll try to smooth
things over with Aki-sama, too.
You're the best, Master!
You're truly the only one I can rely on.
I might not be able to do much, though.
Huh?
It's not like her to say that.
Can't you wait a little longer on the payment?
This is no time to show off.
All right. I'll figure it out.
Well, you seem busy.
I heard you got quite the scolding at home.
Must be hard being a traitor.
It doesn't concern you.
Well, that's not true.
I'm your master's fiancé, after all.
I'm sorry, Adagaki-san!
I was wrong about everything!
Even if you're trying to fabricate everything
and act like the tragic heroine,
I still love you!
Makabe... You'll still love me if I'm fake?
Yes! Putting a lid on our problems!
That's just the right thing to do!
Thank you, Makabe!
Are you okay, Makabe-kun?!
It's no use. Even if there was a way out
of this stalemate, I don't think I'd last.
Did you hit your head?
Uh, no... I'm fine.
You seem rather tired.
Er, yeah... a little bit.
Say, Masamune-sama.
Do you have some time after school?
Huh?
There's somewhere I'd like to go with you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you okay?
Yes. It's just a follow-up.
When you asked me to come with you,
this wasn't what I expected.
Well, Shidou isn't here today.
Yes, yes, I'll take her place today.
Did you think we'd go somewhere
more fitting for a rendezvous?
Wha— I just—
Why don't we take a little walk?
Moderate exercise and saying
everything you're thinking
are both very important to your health.
I see... So that's what happened in Paris.
I'm sure it's my fault for not being able
to hold back and going off on her...
I did think things seemed
a bit different than usual,
but that is quite worrisome.
It is! It's putting my whole
revenge plan in jeopardy.
You still haven't given up on this revenge?
Huh?
Do you want Aki-sama to fall in love with you?
Well... yeah.
Even though you loathe her
and she makes you sick?
Th-That's exactly why I'm going to dump her.
That'll be my revenge, after all.
That's not what you'd call love anymore.
What the heck? Of course it's not.
What's... going on?
I thought I'd be a little courageous.
You're going to choose Adagaki Aki.
But that's for the sake of revenge, not love.
Which would mean that if we fell in love,
you wouldn't be cheating on her.
Fujinomiya-san...
Masamune-sama, I...
Let's run.
Huh?
What in the world is going on?
I'm finally here, Aki-chan.
Sorry, one of the teachers
asked me to do something,
and it took longer than I expected.
No, it's totally fine.
I know, Aki-chan!
Why don't we stop by a family restaurant
on our way home to eat something sweet?
I heard there's some new dessert.
Oh, really? Let's go, then.
You don't mind, right, Yoshino?
Aki-sama, I'm terribly sorry,
but I'd like to head back to the mansion.
Oh, okay...
I wonder what's wrong with Yoshino.
Well, we should get going.
Just a dang minute!
Wh-What's going on, Masamune-sama?
Who are those people?
That's Muriel's big brother.
You know, that girl I met in Paris.
Shit, shit, shit! This definitely has to do
with our teaching Muriel about rom-coms!
That's as far as you're gonna go, guy.
Masamune-sama, I'll throw up
some blood to cause a diversion.
I don't think that'll work
now that you're healthy.
My body has become quite inconvenient.
Don't seem so sad about that.
Where are you trying to
run off to, Chikuwa-kun?
I heard you took good care
of my sister the other day.
Nah, you didn't take care of her at all!
Because you ran off in the middle
of it and went back to Japan!
I had a good reason for that!
Non! I don't want to hear any excuses.
A gun?!
Huh?
If it was up to me, I'd happily
fill you with lead, but alas...
Muriel's manuscript?
After you two left Paris,
my sister kept drawing this.
Even at the expense of eating and sleeping!
Actually, she's gotten a lot better...
I'm assuming she got some
inspiration after seeing you two.
And whatever that inspiration was is why
I'm letting you off the hook just this once.
Um—
I'll just say this. I also prefer happy endings.
Because reality is an absolute shithole.
May I take a look, as well?
S-Sure...
You look awful. Wipe off your face.
My parents are separating.
This time, it's my turn.
I'm gonna keep supporting you
so you can cheer up.
Thank you, but I'm going to go with my dad.
Even then, our hearts will always be together.
Let's see each other again when we're older.
You look awful. Wipe off your face.
I'm surprised you knew it was me.
There's no way I wouldn't be able to tell.
You'll always be you.
The End.
What a cute little story.
Yeah... I guess.
Why didn't we end up like this?
We ended up at odds with each other,
hating and hating back...
Masamune-sama, there's a letter.
Bonjour, Masamune!
I hope you have been well, I do!
I drew a manga inspired by you and Aki.
You never told me how everything ended,
so I gave it my own original ending.
I wish I could become a wall in your
room and learn even more about you.
The walls have ears, and the doors have eyes.
Yours truly, Muriel Besson.
Walls? There's gotta be
a better way to say that...
Let me see that real quick.
Masamune-sama?
This story started out happy,
but in reality, it never got a happy ending.
But if I look at it from
a different perspective...
Is that what's going on here?
The End.
Onii-chan, you're the worst!
My... My spine...
You went into my room without
permission again, didn't you?!
And give me back the panties
and socks you stole the other day!
Huh?! What the hell are you talking about?!
When I looked up at the second floor
from outside, I saw you in my room!
Why from outside?
Because I went to the convenience store.
Hey, are you eating
junk food before dinner again?
The hag's gonna yell at you again.
Don't change the subject!
Ugh, I've had enough!
My brother wears his little sister's
panties on his head!
And he wears just one of his little sister's
socks and stretches it way out!
You're the absolute worse! Keep your
perversion limited to your muscles only!
Now, hang on! My muscles
are absolutely innocent here!
What's the matter, you two?
Huh? Mom, were you just upstairs?
Yes. I was taking you kids'
laundry up to your rooms.
Chinatsu...
H-Huh? Maybe it was just my imagination.
Oh, I know. Want some ice cream, Onii-chan?
No!
Mom! My panties and sock are missing!
Oh, dear. I wonder what happened to them.
How strange.
Where did they go?!
People's minds aren't reliable at all.
What's that? A manuscript?
Maa-kun?
I'm gonna go out for a bit.
But it's almost time for dinner.
Ah! Aki-sama's so cute here!
This lovely Aki-sama, this cute Aki-sama,
and this noble Aki-sama! Give them all to me!
Basically, give me all the Aki-samas!
I guess you really did go to Paris.
We went to the Eiffel Tower,
the Louvre Museum, and Mont-Saint-Michel.
That was pretty rough.
It was pretty far from Paris, too.
Aw, no fair. When I had my trip,
it was just to New York.
At least you were in a place
where people understand English.
I cant even speak English,
so what am I going to do next year?
But, hey... These are all group pictures.
Where are the pictures of
Aki-sama during her free time?
I don't actually have any, sorry.
Hey, hang on a sec!
How worthless are you as a photographer?
Did your battery die at the
critical moment or what?
You're useless.
That's not it. Aki-chan hung out
with Makabe-kun, not me.
What?!
Aki-sama, is that true?
I didn't notice at all!
Sumire... Just a little longer.
Paris
New York
Cebu
Taipei
Honolulu
Los Angeles
Hong Kong
Taipei
London
What?! Sumire collapsed?!
No... I need to know more. How is she doing?
They acted quickly,
so she's stable now, at least...
How many times has it been now?
The fee to keep her in a private
room is already so high...
We don't need a fancy private room!
A shared room would be fine!
Getting Sumire better should come first!
We couldn't possibly blemish
the Gasou name in such a manner!
The only one who needs to be tied down
by conventions, traditions,
and the Gasou name is me.
There's no way I can let Sumire
go through the same thing.
I don't know what happened in Paris,
We need to know more details.
but I can't let her develop any
affection toward Makabe.
Are you listening, Gasou?!
Huh? What?
I held back because you were there!
Whoops, sorry.
Ugh! Aki-sama, are you cheating on us?!
You have all of us and yet you
went to France to go on a date?
Wait, maybe he threatened her.
What?! He won't get away with that!
Absolutely unacceptable!
Could we not talk about that?!
Aki-chan.
If you really feel that way,
stop hanging around Makabe.
Could you give me a little
more thought instead?
I'm going to go wash my hands.
Hey, you!
You're getting way too cozy with her!
You promised you wouldn't pursue her.
I-I know, but I couldn't keep quiet
anymore after what I saw.
The hell are you talking about?!
Look. This is why Aki-chan changed.
Makabe Masamune and Koiwai Yoshino?!
Aki-chan's hurt. She was
betrayed by someone she trusts.
That's why I thought it might be better
to force her to notice someone else.
I see...
Even though this is all a lie,
I win if I can get her to believe it.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but aren't you the little boy
who used to be friends with Aki-sama?
Huh? Um...
I knew right away! You look exactly the same!
gaki Group
Secretary
I'm the secretary to the head
of the Adagaki family.
My name is Yuisaki.
Adagaki...
I'm so glad you remember me!
Where is it? I know it's here somewhere...
Kanetsugu-sama. You haven't even
changed. What are you doing here?
There it is!
What is the meaning of this, Kanetsugu-sama?
The written oath.
The one Grandfather made with
the previous Adagaki family head
when he was still in his prime.
I didn't think a single piece of
paper would do much good,
but if I work this into
everything I heard today,
I'll be able to suck the
Adagaki family funds dry!
I'm going to go marry into their family!
Aki-sama...
Are you okay?
Yes.
Aki-chan...
I'm sorry I suddenly lashed out.
It's okay. You don't have to tell me
what happened if you don't want to,
but if you ever need to talk,
I'll be there for you.
I'm on your side, Aki-chan.
I have no intention of rushing. I'll be
waiting until you're ready, of course.
I'll wait forever for you.
Pig's Foot.
Aki-sama's not here right now.
She had a date with Kanetsugu today.
No, it's fine. That doesn't really matter.
I haven't been here in forever.
This courtyard's much
smaller than I remembered.
It's definitely bigger than mine, though.
Pig's Foot...
It felt like it continued
to the ends of the earth...
But it didn't, of course.
Back in Paris, she had the nerve to act like
she didn't know my Pig's Foot nickname.
Even though she's the one who
called me that when the bullies
were beating the crap out of me here.
That pissed me off.
There was no way I was going
to let her get away with that.
But... What if there's a chance
she's telling the truth?
Thinking that made me feel a little uneasy.
Was the voice I heard here
really Adagaki Aki's?
I don't follow. What are you getting at?
Back then, I thought the only
child in this house was her.
That's why I never even
considered it could be someone else.
According to her, there was another child
her age at this mansion back then,
who couldn't leave her room
because she had chickenpox.
And... that she was
watching us that whole time.
The only ones who know the nickname of
Pig's Foot are me, those bullies, and...
the one who gave me that nickname.
But... Adagaki Aki didn't remember it.
So then...
Why do you call me Pig's Foot?